JOÃO MOREIRA

Junior Full Stack Developer

+351 91 266 95 72

- 🧷 joaomoreira.com
- Vila das Aves, Porto

- @ joaosmoreira86@gmail.com
- linkedin.com/in/joaosmoreira



SUMMARY

With over a decade of professional experience, I have developed skills in various areas, including graphic design, digital marketing and web development. Among my experiences, I've worked for Acushla and Tetribérica, both in digital roles. At Acushla, I mainly focused on developing the company's website and labels for different products and countries, while also participating in production and bottling occasionally. At Tetribérica, I worked in digital marketing, and developed skills in social media marketing, email marketing and website management.

In terms of technical skills, I'm proficient in various software such as Photoshop, Illustrator, Microsoft Office, HubSpot and e-goi.

In addition to my professional experience, I attended a 14-Week Intensive && Immersive Full Stack Programming Bootcamp at <Academia de Código_> with the aim of changing my life. I am highly motivated and eager to learn, and I am excited to take on new challenges and expand my knowledge and skills.

If you're curious, you can see all the positions and companies I've worked for, as well as my entire academic background, on my **LinkedIn.**

EDUCATION

01/2023 - 04/2023

Porto

A 14-Week Intensive && Immersive Full Stack Programming Bootcamp Academia de Código

2013 - 2014

Aves, Porto

Marketing Technician, Marketing Management

EXPERIENCE

01/2021 - Present

Graphic Design

Aves, Porto

Freelancer

Apparel Design / Social Media / Product Design

01/2020 - 05/2020

Aves, Porto

Production Support

DUX Beds & Furniture

05/2015 - 01/2017

Graphic Design & Digital Marketing

Trofa, Porto

Acushla, SA

Although the focus of the work was on developing the company's website and labels for different products and countries, I occasionally participated in the production and bottling.

· Social Media Marketing / Product Design and Development

02/2015 - 04/2015

Digital Marketing / Internship

Trofa, Porto

Tetribérica, SA

· Social Media Marketing / Market Research & Analysis / HubSpot / e-goi / Web Development

SKILLS

Gitlab	Github	REST APIs	JUnit	Tomo	at S	pring Fra	mework	Spring MVC	ECMASci	ript SOAP
jQuery	Java	Bootstrap	JDBC	MVC	ООР	css	HTML	Web Apps	Web Dev	Testing
SCRUM	Agile N	Methodologies	Mave	n SQ	L Ja	vaScript				